/*Name: Vibha Prahlada 
  Course Name: Web Programming 1
  Assignment Number: 2
  Date of Submission: 10-29-2012 */
var geoQuestions =[{question:  "Where is the great Barrier Reef?", 
					questionType:  1, 
					choices: [ "Africa", "N.America","S.America","Australia"],
					correctChoice: "Australia",
					score: 5,
					hint:"It has one of the best beaches in the World."
					},
					{question:  "What planet is Curiosity Rover on now?", 
					questionType:  2, 
					correctChoice: "MARS",
					score: 5,
					hint: " This is the 4th planet from the sun and next planet to EARTH"
					},
					{question: "Which Among these is the largest country in Middle East in area?",
					questionType: 1,
					choices: ["Egypt","Saudi Arabia","Iran","Iraq"],
					correctChoice:"Saudi Arabia",
					score: 5,
					hint:" This country has the world's second largest oil reserve."
					},
					{question:"What is the term for a part of an ocean or sea that cuts far into the bordering landmass and may contain one or more bays?",
					questionType: 2,
					correctChoice:"GULF",
					score: 5,
					hint:"The GULF of MEXICO is one of them."
					},
					{question:"Which state has a climate suitable for growing citrus fruits",
					questionType:1,
					choices:["California","Maine","New York","Alaska"],
					correctChoice:"California",
					score:5,
					hint:"Bay Area!! Does it ring a bell!!"
					},
					{question:"The great Victoria Desert is located in",
					questionType:1,
					choices:["Canada", "West Africa", "Australia", "North America"],
					correctChoice:"Australia",
					score:5,
					hint:"It is the native of Kangaroos and Koalas."
					},
					{question:"The leading state in India in producing paper is",
					questionType:2,
					correctChoice:"WEST BENGAL",
					score:5,
					hint:"This state in INDIA is famous for Tigers and Rabindranath Tagore is from this region!"
					},
					{question:"The largest gold producing country in the world is",
					questionType:2,
					correctChoice:"CHINA",
					score:5,
					hint:"2008 olympics was held in this country."
					},
					{question:"The largest country of the world by geographical area is",
					questionType:1,
					choices:["Russia","Vatican City", "Australia", "USA"],
					correctChoice:"Russia",
					score:5,
					hint:"Moscow is the capital of this counrty."
					},
					{question:"The largest Continent in the world is",
					questionType:2,
					correctChoice:"ASIA",
					score:5,
					hint:"This continent hosts 60% of the world's current human population."
					}];